A Finding Aid to the Donald Saff papers and Saff Tech Arts Records, circa 1710, 1800-2013 bulk 1965-2010, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Saff Tech Arts Records, circa 1970-2013; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 22.2 Linear feet Boxes 10-32, 34; .640 Gigabytes ER010-ER011
  - Artist Files, circa 1970-2010; 2.2; Archival Resource Key; 15.2 Linear feet Boxes 12-27, 33; 0.64 Gigabytes ER010-ER011
    - Robert Rauschenberg, Archival Resource Key
      - Exhibition,Taejŏn Expo '93 (Aug.-Nov. 1993), Archival Resource Key
        - Marketing Echo-Echo, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 7)
        - Damage, Insurance Claim, Echo-Echo, circa 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 8)
        - Insurance, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 9)
        - Shipping, Artpack, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - Exhibition, Scores (Off Kilter Keys) (Feb. 1994), circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - Exhibition, Kunst Sammlung Nordhein-Westfalen (May 1994), circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - Exhibition, Akira Ikeda Gallery (Unrealized, Scheduled May-June 1994), circa 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 13)
      - Exhibition, São Paulo Art Biennial (Fall 1994), circa 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 14)
      - Exhibition, Prints Retrospective at National Gallery of Art, Ruth Fine Catalog Essay, circa1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Exhibition, Museum of Contemporary Art, Miami (Apr.-Jun,1996), circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 16-17)
      - Exhibition, Helsinki Festival, Krista Mikkola (Unrealized), circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Exhibition, Art for the World, San Lazzaro, Venice (Jun-Jul. 1996), circa 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 19-20)
      - Exhibition, Donald Saff/Robert Rauschenberg: In Collaboration (Feb. 1997) Loan, Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Exhibition: Guggenheim Museum Retrospective (Sep. 1997-Jan.1998), Archival Resource Key
        - General, circa 1995-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 22)
        - Correspondence, General, circa 1995-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 23)
        - Correspondence, Guggenheim, circa 1995-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 24-25)
        - Correspondence, Untitled Press, circa 1994-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 26)
        - Correspondence, Billy Kluver, Julie Martin, 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 27)
        - Catalogue, circa 1995-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 28-30)
        - Checklist, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 31)
        - Expenses, circa 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 32)
        - Press, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 33)
        - Fact Checking, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 34)
      - Exhibition, Robert Rauschenberg: A Retrospective Menil Collection (Feb. 1998), circa 1995-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Exhibition, Bilbao Guggenheim (Nov. 1998), Archival Resource Key
        - Opening, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 2)
        - Correspondence, circa 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 3-4)
      - Exhibition, Cage 108 Design by Rauschenberg (Apr. 2000), circa 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Exhibition, Vanderbilt University (Jan.-Mar. 2004), circa 2004; Archival Resource Key; Includes born-digital records; see ER010. (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Exhibition, Vanderbilt University (Jan.-Mar. 2004), Installation Images, Digital Photographs, Archival Resource Key; 0.629 Gigabytes Twenty-two computer files (Folder ER010)
      - Exhibition, Palazzo dei Diamanti (Feb.-Jun. 2004) Rachel Rosenthal & Co., circa 2002-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Exhibition, Wexner Center for the Arts (Oct. 2005-Frb. 2006), circa 2005-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Loan, Ringling Museum, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Loan, National Gallery of Art, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Anagrams, Archival Resource Key
        - Correspondence, Pace Wildenstein, circa 1996-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 11-13)
        - Marketing and PR, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 14)
        - Sales Prices, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 15)
        - Accounting (1996), circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 16)
        - Accounting (1997), circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 17)
        - Accounting (1998), circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 18)
        - Exhibition, Mirthday Man (Anagram) Otsuka Museum of Art (Mar. 1998), circa 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 19)
      - Ancient Incident, Correspondence, Douglas Chrismas, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 20)
      - Apogamy Pods, General, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 21)
      - Arcadian Retreats (Frescoes), Archival Resource Key
        - General, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 22)
        - Series Details, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 23)
        - David Adamson Editions, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 24)
        - Correspondence, Guggenheim Museum, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 25)
        - Correspondence, Untitled Press, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 26)
        - Correspondence, Fresco Jammer, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 27)
        - Correspondence, Pace Wildenstein, circa 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 28)
        - Consignment, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 29)
        - Sales, circa 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 30)
        - Accounting, circa 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 31)
        - Press, circa 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 32)
      - Cock-Sure, Documentation, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 33)
      - Copperhead Chica, Sale, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 34)
      - Doubleluck, Sale, Pace Wildenstein, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 35)
      - Echo-Echo, Archival Resource Key
        - General, circa 1992-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 36)
        - Sales, Galerie Jamileh Weber, circa 1994-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 37)
        - Sale, Seattle Symphony, circa 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 38)
      - Fabric Project, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Fanfare, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Fish Park, circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Lotus Series, circa 2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Parliament, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Prime Pump, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Quattro Man IV, 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Raspberry Crime, circa 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Riding Bikes, circa 1995-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Rite to Fly, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Shales Series, Archival Resource Key
        - General, circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 11)
        - Correspondence, Bernard Jacobson Gallery, circa 1995-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 12-13)
        - Exhibition, Knoedler & Co. (Sep.-Oct. 1994), circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 14)
        - Exhibition, Galerie Templon (Feb. 1995), circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 15)
        - Exhibition, Galerie Templon (Feb. 1995), Correspondence, Daniel Templon, circa 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 16)
        - Exhibition, Galerie Templon (Feb. 1995), Correspondence, Outgoing STA, circa 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 17)
        - Exhibition, Galerie Templon (Feb. 1995), Correspondence, Outgoing (Captiva), circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 18)
        - Exhibition, Galerie Templon (Feb. 1995), Correspondence, Legal, Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 19)
        - Exhibition, Galerie Templon (Feb. 1995), Correspondence, Leo Castelli Gallery, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 20)
        - Exhibition, Galerie Templon (Feb. 1995), Sales, Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 21)
        - Exhibition, Galerie Templon (Feb. 1995), Shipping, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 22)
        - Exhibition, Galerie Templon (Feb. 1995), Press, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 23)
        - Exhibition, Galerie Jamileh Weber (Unrealized), circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 24)
      - Sor Aqua, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 25)
      - Soundings, circa 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 26)
      - Stake-Out, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 27)
      - Sterling Whirl, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 28)
      - Synapsis Shuffle, Archival Resource Key
        - Exhibition, Whitney Museum (June 2000), General, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 29)
        - Exhibition, Whitney Museum (June 2000), Correspondence, Whitney Museum, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 30-31)
      - Tribute 21 Print Portfolio, Felissimo, circa 1994-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 32)
      - Untitled, 1953, Sale, circa 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 33)
      - Venus Rapture IV, Correspondence, Sash Spencer, circa 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 34)
      - Untitled Press Artwork Numbers, Archival Resource Key
        - UP1001, 30 Photographs, Larry Rubin, Zeltweg Fine Arts, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 35)
        - UP1002, Budget Cut, Pace Wildenstein, 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 36)
        - UP1003 Anagrams, Pace Wildenstein, 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 37)
        - UP1004 Anagrams, Pace Wildenstein, 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 38)
        - UP1005 Holiday Ruse, Menil Collection, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 39)
        - UP1006-UP1007 Pace Wildenstein, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 40)
        - UP1008 Anagrams, Curtain Call, Zeltweg Fine Arts, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 41)
        - UP1009 Anagrams, Pace Wildenstein, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 42)
        - UP1010 Lisa Fugue #4, Ann Wyckoff, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 43)
        - UP1011 Anagrams, Galerie Jamileh Weber, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 44)
        - UP1012 Anagrams, Pace Wildenstein, 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 45)
        - UP1013 Anagrams, Pace Wildenstein, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 46)
        - UP1014 Holiday Ruse, Menil Collection, 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 47)
        - UP1015 Untitled (Matte Black...), Pace Wildenstein, circa 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 48)
        - UP1016 Individual (From Seven Characters), Gemini GEL, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 49)
        - UP1017 Barge, Guggenheim Museum, circa 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 50)
        - UP1018 Anagrams, Pace Wildenstein, 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 51)
        - UP1019 Anagrams, Pace Wildenstein, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 52)
        - UP1020 Anagrams, Pace Wildenstein, 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 53)
        - UP1021 Holiday Ruse, Menil Collection, 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 54)
        - UP1022 Hives (Anagrams), circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 55)
        - UP1023 Blue Eagle, Pace Wildenstein, 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 56)
        - UP1024 Pace Wildenstein, circa 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 57)
        - UP1025 Anagrams, Pace Wildenstein, 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 58)
        - UP1026 Anagrams, Pace Wildenstein, 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 59)
        - UP1027 11 Photographs, Zeltweg Fine Art, circa 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 60)
        - UP1028 Blue Eagle, Pace Wildenstein, circa 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 61)
        - UP1029 Eight Drawings, Guggenheim Museum, circa 1999, 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 62)
        - UP1030 Synapsis Shuffle, Invoices, Pace Wildenstein, circa 1999-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 63-34)
        - UP1031 Pace Wildenstein, circa 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 1)
        - UP1032 Apogamy Pods, Esther Grether, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 2)
        - UP1033 Hoarfrost, Texas Gallery, circa 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 3)
        - UP1034 Galerie Jamileh Weber, circa 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 4)
        - UP1035 Naples Anagram, Eckert Gallery, circa 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 5)
        - UP1036 Galerie Jamileh Weber, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 6)
        - UP1037 Everglade, Louisa Sarofim, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 7)
        - UP1038 Anagram, Texas Gallery, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 8)
        - UP1039 Monkey Bum, Texas Gallery, circa 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 9)
        - UP1040 Eight Apogamy Pods, Pace Wildenstein, circa 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 10)
        - UP1041 Apogamy Pods, Eckert Gallery, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - Rauschenberg Overseas Culture Interchange (ROCI), Archival Resource Key
        - Correspondence, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 12)
        - Chronology, circa 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 13)
        - Interviews, Various (1981-1987), circa 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 14-15)
        - Exhibition, National Gallery of Art (Apr.-Sep. 1991) Opening (Apr. 22 1991), circa 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 16)
        - Exhibition, National Gallery of Art (Apr.-Sep. 1991) Chronology, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 17)
        - Exhibition, National Gallery of Art (Apr.-Sep. 1991) Travel Expenses, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 18)
        - Exhibition, National Gallery of Art (Apr.-Sep. 1991) Captiva Shipping, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 19)
        - Exhibition, Wax Fire Works, Knoedler & Co. (May-June 1991), circa 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 20)
        - Exhibition, Wax Fire Works, Knoedler & Co. (May-June 1991), Invoices, circa 1990-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 21)
        - Exhibition, Wax Fire Works, Knoedler & Co. (May-June 1991) Crate Packing List, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 22)
        - ROCI Mexico City, circa 1985-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 23)
        - ROCI Mexico City, circa 1985-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 24)
        - Inventory, ROCI Works, circa 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 25)
        - Narcissus Documentation, circa 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 26)
        - Pegasits Documentation, circa 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 27)
        - Pegasits Shipment, Donald Schwartz, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 28)
        - Seminole Host Documentation, circa 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 29)
        - Seminole Host Documentation, circa 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 30)
        - Swim Documentation, circa 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 31)
        - Swim, Sales Correspondence, Corrado Frederico, circa 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 32)
        - Frames, Engle Metal Fabrication, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 33)
        - Sculpture Handling Instructions, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 34)
        - Project Notes, circa 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 35)
      - Inventory, circa 1990-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 36-39)
      - Inventory, Price Lists, circa 1998-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Consignment, circa 1996-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Consignment, circa 1998-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 3-4)
      - Sales Quotations, circa 1996-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Sales, Fish Park, Hiroshima City Museum, circa 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Sales, MoMA, Pace Wildenstein, circa 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Sales, Bleacher Series, Pace MacGill, circa 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Sales, Guggenheim Museum Drawings, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Sales, Barge, Guggenheim Bilbao, circa 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 10-12)
      - Sales, Pace Prints, circa 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - Sales Christies Auction (Fall 1997), circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 14)
      - Invoices, circa 1998-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 15-16)
      - Invoices, circa 1994-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 17)
      - Invoices, Untitled Press, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 18)
      - Invoices, Atlantic Van Line (Shipping), circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 19)
      - Report, Projected STA Income for 2000, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 20)
      - Report, Commission Due Don Saff, circa 1998-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 21)
      - Documentary (Karen Thomas, Film Odyssey), circa 1995-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 22-23)
      - Writings, Biography, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Writings "Rauschenberg, Counter-Rauschenberg" by Brian O'Doherty, 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Writings, Interview with Martin Gayford, Sunday Telegraph (Oct. 17, 1997), circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Writings, "The Celebration of Otherness" Larry Day, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Writings, Seminar UNESCO in Venice" Art: Tolerance and Intolerance (Dec. 1995), circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Notes, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Documentation, Miscellaneous, circa 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Event, Party at NYC, Great Performances (Sep. 9. 1997), circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Gifts, Christmas, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 9-10)
      - Gifts, Christmas, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 11)
      - Gifts, Christmas, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - RR Travel Itineraries, circa 1996-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - STA Visit (June 1991), circa 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 14)
      - STA Visit (July 1992), circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 15)
      - Wax Information, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 16)
      - Wax Color Tests, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 17)
      - Signatures, circa 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 18)
      - Printed Material, National Medal of Arts, White House, NEA, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 19)
      - Printed Material, Press Clippings, circa 1990-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 20-22)
      - Printed Material, ROCI, Press Clippings, circa 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 23)
      - Printed Material, ROCI, Miscellaneous, circa 1990-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 24)
      - Printed Material, Miscellaneous, circa 1990s-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 25)
      - Printed Material, Oversize Invitations, 1990, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - Photographs of Rauschenberg, circa 1970s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 26)
      - Photographs of DJS and RR in Asia, circa 1985-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 27)
      - Photographs of Captiva, FL, circa 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - James Rosenquist, Archival Resource Key
      - Correspondence, Archival Resource Key
        - General, circa 1981, 1991-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 29-30)
        - General (Oversized), circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 9)
        - Anita Friedman Fine Arts, 2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 31)
        - Bernard Jacobson Gallery, circa 2000-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 34)
        - Julia Blaut (Guggenheim Museum, circa 2000-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 35)
        - Mary A. Dreblow (May Clinic Advisor), circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 36)
        - Eckert Fine Art, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 37)
        - Galerie Jamileh Weber, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 38)
        - Florida Arts Council (Florida Hall of Fame), circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 39)
        - Gagosian Gallery, circa 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 40)
        - Kunstmuseum Wolfsburg, circa 2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 41)
        - Aaron Levine, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 42)
        - Beverly McCoe (Rosenquist Studio), circa 2000-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 43)
        - Pace Wildenstein, circa 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 44)
        - Sonnabend Gallery, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 45)
        - Sotheby's, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 46)
        - University of Southern Florida (USF), circa 2000-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 47)
      - Exhibition, Archival Resource Key
        - James Rosenquist Time Dust Complete Graphics 1962 - 1992 (Traveling), circa 1993-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 1)
        - An Evening with James Rosenquist (May 7, 1999) Academy of the Arts, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 2)
        - Rosenquist Mural at Guggenheim Soho Viewing (Mar. 1 2000), circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 3)
        - James Rosenquist: Paintings, James Rosenquist Selects Dali Dali Museum (Apr.-May 2000), circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 4)
        - Sarasota Biennial (July-Nov. 2000) Ringling Museum of Art, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 5)
        - The Universe, Armory Center for the Arts, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 6)
        - Guggenheim Retrospective (Oct. 2003-Feb. 2004), Correspondence, General, circa 2000-2003; Archival Resource Key; Includes one optical disc, cd-r. (Box 27, Folder 7)
        - Guggenheim Retrospective (Oct. 2003-Feb. 2004), Digital Documents, Archival Resource Key; 0.011 Gigabytes Eleven computer files (Folder ER011)
        - Guggenheim Retrospective (Oct. 2003-Feb. 2004), Correspondence, Sarah Bancroft, circa 2001-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 8)
        - Guggenheim Retrospective (Oct. 2003-Feb. 2004), Contract, circa 2000-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 9)
        - Price Lists with Dimensions, circa 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 10)